Said sir, their chassis alignment is not there, from where you stop the stopper,
there is no alignment, the dot is not given, it is NOT successful.
Sir anything can happen to a bike
Thats what I am saying I cant take risk
talking about now . IF in future accident happens we would be the one to suffer. What are you talking about here [MUSIC]
Blogs so gas right now our Honda which is lying in Ranchi's Horizon Honda service center if you
guys don't know then I told in the last video that we met with an accident and after that
we serviced our bike It has been given at the center, now we went to the insurance claim center
and on the same day we completed the process of insurance claim which is paper work, then
they told that in a day or two you will get Will tell what will be the cost after the inspection,
if the parts are to be repaired, today it has been 2 to 3 days and the call has been received twice;
Manoj ji, the people of Honda service center who are looking at my insurance claim there,
Manoj ji told me in the evening that sir, your car will cost around 52-5000
I had told him the time, so he was telling that my soaker , which is the soaker of T section,
one of the two sockers has been damaged, so one soaker will have to be replaced,
so I asked him whether it would be right to replace one soaker or both. If it is replaced
together, then he told that no sir, there is no problem, I have to confirm a little bit,
but after that the handle is also going to be completely replaced, it will not be repaired,
the headlight is also broken . She was dimming the lights but the headlight was provided,
so don't know how but they are saying that they will replace it, it is a complete plus, it will
be a complete replacement, it will fit there, we will also fit in tank. If there was a dent in
the tank, then the dent and paint will be less, the tank is not going to be replaced, but there is
a dent in it, the handle which was worn due to break at the stop, has a dent in it and scratches
also came. If it is, then they will repair the whole thing, after that they will repeat it,
then this is what is going to happen, the tank is not going to be replaced, now I understand that
much. I was thinking that all these things are going to happen but I am telling the new thing
that he has told me and it is surprising me a bit, he said that the whole thing is needed.
sir apna 50 plus
more hurt aayi but he is telling that which is your stopper which if you do not know then
the stopper which is the handle of your handlebar which has handlebar its sorry
not the handlebar which goes to the stem nor below like yours which connects below
the handlebar If it happens, then there are two such that they come from the stopper,
they come from valid already means as well as they live very well in the world,
what is less of it that if the handle of your bike somehow rotates more in any one side If it goes,
it is not allowed to move more than a fixed level, it is stopped there, then it is very important,
especially if you go off-road etc. or suddenly your handle gets jerked, then they are saying that
if we weld etc. then there can be a problem in it again, so they are recommending and saying
that as many times as this case has come in the past in which the key is broken at the stop,
then the whole will have to be changed, so I said ok Hey friend, if needed then do it
because it will come on top of insurance but this is where the problem comes, yesterday he had told
his estimate. And after that in the evening probably the inspection officer came means
from ICICI Lombard, because my insurance is from ICICI Lombard, then the problem comes there, now
what is the problem that the ICICI officer came, whatever they checked If there is an infection,
then they are saying that there is no need to change the key itself, you just do the welding,
then we will do the welding, it will be repaired and we will repair it, and for this reason,
Manoj ji again in the morning. Called and they told me that the effect is such that the people
of ICICI infection have come and gone saying that we will repair it by welding and give it
back because the service center people themselves are saying that Sir, this cannot be repaired,
he has repeatedly eaten this thing that Sir, we do not repair this thing, we are the director.
There is also a proof that I have recorded everything and everything, because in the
matter of insurance, I always face some or the other problem, people try to save their
money, I have kept that also recorded For the time being, Sanjay Sir has been alerted by the
infection officer for me, so he is telling that I talked to him only, he is telling that Sir,
it is not such a big issue, it is a very small issue, it will be easily repaired by welding.
So Manoj ji is also saying the same thing sir, repair is done but he does it in small vehicles,
now he does it in small vehicles, now he does it in 200 cc and 150 cc vehicles, your 180k bike
will do it If you have a specialty in bikes, this thing does not reduce all the bikes in Big Honda.
that will change
given alignment
which does not align
dot is given
[music]